[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Batmans sidekick Robin was originally drawn in a rather flamboyant suit of red, green, and yellow. Who was this suit modeled after?", "correct_answer": "Robin Hood", "incorrect_answers": ["The Vision", "The Scarlette Pimpernell", "The Three Musketeers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is the sweat of the Hippopotamus?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Clear", "Pink", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bread is one of the oldest prepared foods.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What natural therapy works best for seasonal depression and low moods due to sleep deprivation?", "correct_answer": "Bright light therapy", "incorrect_answers": ["Water therapy", "Aromatherapy", "Massage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the address of the museum in which Mickeys dad works in the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "441 -8th Street", "incorrect_answers": ["448 -8th Street", "444 -8th Street", "442 -8th Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Ralphies fathers first name in the film A Christmas Story?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Ralph Senior", "Walter", "Franklin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If one were to look at the sky from Plutos surface, every 17 hours they would observe exceptionally beautiful rises of Charon because of its closeness to Pluto.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alfred Hitchcock was born in Leytonstone, London in what year?", "correct_answer": "1899", "incorrect_answers": ["1911", "1917", "1889"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Camp Rock is a 2008 Disney Channel Original Movie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 21, which member of the team gets kicked off after becoming drunk and spilling a drink on another member?", "correct_answer": "Fisher", "incorrect_answers": ["Choi", "Ben Campbell", "Kianna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the movie Whats Love Got to Do With It?", "correct_answer": "Brian Gibson", "incorrect_answers": ["F. Gary Gray", "Tina Turner", "Laurence Fishburne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lionel Sterberger grilled the first cheeseburger in 1945.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]